The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Boss !
What is that ?
Boss,
I found a money tree !
What an ugly kid...
If we break his legs,
we can use him as bait for the Heavenly Power Escort.
It’s better than using our own brother !
Take him.
Street\NCountry of Suzaku
At that moment
Ceng Niu raised two fingers,
ready to perish together with Red Butterfly.
After hearing about the duel...
Red Butterfly refused to back down.
Red Butterfly also made a breakthrough,
she's now trying to reach Soul Transformation.
She's the proud daughter of Xue Yue,
to make her submit back then
the country of Suzaku paid a hefty price.
I know you hid a tiny bit of your Origin Soul somewhere.
Heartless,
I won’t allow a second cauldron to escape.
Ceng Niu's duel with Red Butterfly made him famous,
solidifying his title as the strongest person under Soul Transformation.
But who would’ve thought
that the very next day
Ceng Niu would vanish.
What ?
Ceng Niu’s gone ?
Is it true ?
Cave at the top of\NMount Suzaku\NCountry of Suzaku
Disciple humbly requests that Master comes out.
I have heard.
That brat
disappeared suddenly.
Disciple is sorry
for interrupting Master's seclusion.
Don't worry,
he is the cauldron I chose for you.
It's not a big deal
but...
Well, it kind of is...
Yesterday, I sensed a surge
of celestial spiritual energy in the far north.
It most likely was Soul Transformation cultivators fighting.
I found that
Wang Lin’s disappearance
is because of Xue Yue
and the Giant Demon Clan.
This jade slip can track him.
He’s gravely injured,
his Origin Soul collapsed.
I can only sense
that he’s in the north of the Suzaku continent.
Abandonned temple\NCountry of Pilu
I cultivated for 500 years
just to become mortal again.
But in 8 years,
Wan’er will face the law of the heavens again.
8 years...
If my original body was here,
I would find a place rich in spiritual energy
to cultivate again.
I would've been able to recover.
But my original body
was also affected by the collapse of my Origin Soul.
It fell into a deep sleep under the country of Chu.
Maybe
I can find a local cultivation sect
and they will have places with dense spiritual energy.
But...
in my current state...
how could I even enter a sect ?
What must I do
to break the seal and domain
restriction on my body ?
Within 100 li,
we can’t afford to offend Immortals.
But in mortal territory,
even the officials need to respect us !
Village chief\NFire Cloud Village
Yet the Heavenly Power Escort dares to ignore us.
They think they can take a detour.
Alright,
let’s teach them a lesson !
Yes !
The Heavenly Power Escort would never expect
that we’d ambush them here.
Boss,
you're brilliant !
It's genius !
The time is about right,
get ready.
Got it !
This ugly face
makes the perfect bait.
Little brat,
consider yourself unlucky.
What's this look ?
Let’s go.
On my way !
Fire...
Fire Cloud Poison !
It's activated by fire.
Shit !
Fire Cloud Poison !
Cover your mouths !
Retreat !
Charge in !
Go !
Give me that !
Trying to flee ?
Loot them !
Everyone has returned !
Open the gates !
Fire Cloud Village\NCountry of Pilu
The boss is back !
Hurry !
With the boss leading us
the haul is always different.
It should be enough to enjoy for a while.
Fetch some good wine
and let the brothers
drink their fill tonight !
Got it !
Be careful with him,
throw him in the water prison.
Let's keep him
for next time.
Understood.
It seems that
a cultivator that has lost everything
is even worse than a mortal…
Wan’er,
this time
it's going to be hard.
But I will brave these obstacles
and return to you.
I need spiritual energy to break the chains
and to restore my cultivation.
Isn't this...
It’s really spiritual energy !
This water contains spiritual energy !
If I can absorb it,
I can escape this place.
Enter my body...
Return to the origin...
Good haul today !
Indeed !
We slaughtered a fat sheep.
What’s this ?
Boss,
I took this off that ugly brat.
Isn't this
Heavenly Silkworm Thread ?
I don’t believe it !
A treasure...
This is a real treasure !
Yes, yes!
If we can get more of these
and weave them into armor,
we’d be invincible !
I wonder where that ugly brat got it.
I’ll ask him.
Boss, he's here.
Boss, the water...
Something’s in the water !
Bullshit !
Drag him out now !
You...
Who are you ?!
That day,
you broke my limbs.
N-no !
It wasn't me !
It's... him!
He told me to do it !
Please spare me !
I was
blind to your greatness !
Shut up.
Immortal !
I was wrong !
Let me go !
The treasures,
my village,
they're all yours !
Spare me, Immortal !
Please spare me !
My spiritual energy
isn't enough
to kill him.
But I can open my bag of holding...
Mosquito Beast !
Demon Beast...
A Demon Beast !
Kill him.
A monster !
A Demon Beast !
Spare me !
Immortal, spare me !
Spare me, Immortal !
Paying respects to Immortal !
Where am I ?
Immortal,
this is Fire Cloud Village of the country of Pilu.
How long will it take
to dig out this prison ?
th.. th.. thr..
Three days !
One day,
we can do it in one day.
Start now then.
Immortal,
it’s all done.
From now on,
no one leaves the village.
Dismissed.
Yes !
Go, quick.
This isn’t a Spirit Vein,
so why does this water have spiritual energy ?
Top quality spirit stones ?
No wonder...
Sealed with 5 top quality spirit stones...
This corpse must’ve been very powerful.
It's best not act recklessly.
I never managed to understand what this scroll is,
but even Mu Ye of the Forsaken Immortal Clan coveted it.
Note: the 7-leaf Shaman
It must hold unimaginable power.
How did you find
this water prison ?
R... Reporting to Immortal,
this was just a barren land a few years ago.
But after an earthquake
the mountain split open
and this place appeared.
Then...
The boss thought it'd make a good prison
so we built this water prison.
Who was that corpse ?
What's its connection to this scroll ?
And what's this purple light ?
Alright,
I can't rush this matter.
For now, I must focus on restoring my cultivation
and breaking the seal.
The spiritual energy's violent impact
forced open a tiny crack in the seal.
But this method
can't be used again.
The seal doesn't just block spiritual energy
but it also devours it.
To open a larger crack
I need to accumulate internal spiritual energy
and advance my cultivation.
That way I can attack it from both sides at once
to weaken it further.
6 months later
After 6 months,
I'm only at the 6th layer of Qi Condensation.
This seal and domain combination is truly overbearing.
It's time to break it !
It's devouring more energy than before...
My spiritual energy won't last long.
This won't work !
To further weaken the seal
I can only think of one way.
If I swallow a celestial jade,
I can fight poison with poison.
Three...
Two...
One !
Break !
I did it !
Wang Lin's avatar\NEarly stage\NFoundation Establishment
Be quiet,
don't disturb the Immortal.
This breakthrough
dispersed 10 percent of the Tea Domain
and loosend the sealing mark.
I can now use
most of my artifacts.
Thanks to the Mosquito Beast,
as long as I don't meet Soul Formation cultivators,
I will be safe.
No matter what,
within 7 years,
I must recover my cultivation.
I don't have enough top quality spirit stones
to keep using them like this.
I need a place dense in spiritual energy to cultivate.
Like the Soul Refining Sect...
Soul Refining Sect\NCountry of Pilu
One of Pilu's three great sects.
They must have
abundant spiritual energy.
To let go of the consequences of my actions
is to ignore the law of cause and effect
like scattered ink.
As destiny falls
in exchange for this moment of tainted dreams.
It makes the mountains lose their colors,
wither and melt into rivers.
Who can deceive
the law of the heavens ?
Countless generations
have tried before me.
But how could I not catch my dreams
within my warm fingers ?
You're at my side when I'm alone
giving me the strength to fight the will of the heavens.
Fortunately, my mind was open and honest.
I'm sorry we never got to see the fireworks
in the streets.
Can I break the vortex of our destiny ?
Can I break the rules ?
To run towards you !
I will fight the law of the heavens and the law of cause and effect
to cut down this tribulation with my own hands
and break through the reincarnation cycle.
All of that for the stars in your eyes.
I wish to bend this dream for the fire in my heart.
If your soul is willing to wander,
can I still take your hands
and hold them tight ?
I will defy the heavens and prevent the stars from falling.
I will overthrow the Immortals and the Demons in my heart.
I dream of destroying
the shackles of our fate.
You're the only one that can ignore the law of cause and effect.
You're the hardest to let go of.
I want to be with you again
so I can look in your eyes.
Even for a moment, it's worth it.